<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">
    <string-array name="fullchangelog">
        <item>@array/v105</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="v105">
        <item>hyaku go</item>
        <item>IMPORTANT: If you haven\'t rebooted yet, REBOOT IN 2 MINUTES AFTER APPLYING/UPDATING!</item>
        <item>ATTENTION!!: This is a monthly build now, as I started school and I have much more responsibilities now, I can\'t juggle both CMTE, Layers and ROM source verification as well as assignments. From now on, I will accept requests, and only push out updates when deemed enough of an update. Please respect my decision and I would be grateful if you joined my G+ community instead of spamming my mailbox to post bugs, as other users can help answer your issue.</item>
        <item>Revert back to previous fonts to prevent switching problems, AGAIN! No more complaints, please!</item>
        <item>Add themed QS volume panel tile.</item>
        <item>Add QS On-the-Go QS Tiles and Power Menu buttons.</item>
        <item>Add themed notification drawer button to switch from Task Manager.</item>
        <item>Replace contextual headers with new poly effect backgrounds by @BellaxMiu</item>
        <item>Revamp ES File Explorer drawer text, thanks to @franzyroy.</item>
        <item>Fix Chrome Dev\'s Unreadable bookmarks.</item>
        <item>Pushbullet: Fix unreadable text colors for popup and search box.</item>
        <item>Do not use publicized styles, call privatized ones instead.</item>
        <item>Fix G+ Poll colors and reorganize cdt colors.</item>
        <item>Fix unreadable text in Smart Lock "Places" activity and change header text in Google Settings.</item>
        <item>Add inverted Google+ Overlay.</item>
        <item>Add darkened button bar for Twitter.</item>
        <item>Update Bluetooth connected status bar icon.</item>
        <item>Fix OK Google Voice Training Text Colors.</item>
        <item>Update YouTube Overlay for 10.35.53.</item>
        <item>Add colorful Google icons into search bar and SystemUI\'s nav target.</item>
        <item>Theme Snapdragon Browser (Cyanogen OS 12.1 edition).</item>
        <item>Theme GalleryNext (Cyanogen OS 12.1 edition).</item>
        <item>Theme DialerNext (Cyanogen OS 12.1 edition).</item>
        <item>Add colored drawables for legacy Google Search apps.</item>
        <item>Fix invisible Cyanogen Theme Chooser App Themer text color.</item>
        <item>Bliss: Add exposed text color on DPI alert dialog.</item>
        <item>Fix unreadable status change window in Hangouts.</item>
        <item>WhatsApp: Change accent to green, and darken card colors.</item>
        <item>Bliss: Add new QS Panel and QS Bar tiles.</item>
        <item>Add themed KatPro notification text color.</item>
        <item>Add themed Shuttle and Shuttle+ notification colors.</item>
        <item>Fix invisible Root and SD card icon in history of ESFileExplorer.</item>
        <item>Fix Google Play Music Tutorial Buttons.</item>
        <item>Whiten YouTube search clear all button.</item>
        <item>Fix YouTube text after typing in searchbox/actionbar.</item>
        <item>Fix unreadable Frequently Contacted contact text colors.</item>
        <item>Adjust Chrome tab text color and remove text shadows.</item>
        <item>Re-add default text color to fix unreadable popups in Chrome.</item>
        <item>Revert "Fix Chrome Bookmarks Invisible Text".</item>
        <item>Add new WhatsApp Compose Icons by @arjerine.</item>
        <item>Remove legacy Google Logo from Google Search Bar.</item>
        <item>Hangouts Blocked People drawable - inverted the question marks.</item>
        <item>Fix Google Play Services v8 - Popup menu black on black.</item>
        <item>Drop support for Hangouts 3.0.</item>
        <item>Change Hangouts overlay to use green instead of grey.</item>
        <item>Add new Dropbox authenticator icon.</item>
        <item>Fix BetterBatteryStats status bar color.</item>
        <item>Fix Google Play Games Settings status bar.</item>
        <item>Fix unreadable Google Play Games progress circle.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>